<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- example file containing base tags -->

<game>	
	<title>Epic Golf 2D</title>
	<release-date>1 May, 2019</release-date>
	<website>http://www.golf2d.online/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>PC / Mac</name>
			<!-- <link>http://www.gamesite.com/</link> -->
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam</name>
			<!-- <link>http://www.steampowered.com/</link> -->
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Apple App Store</name>
			<!-- <link>http://www.itunes.com/</link> -->
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Play Store</name>
			<!-- <link>http://www.itunes.com/</link> -->
		</platform>
	</platforms>

	<prices>
		<price>
			<currency>F2P</currency>
			<value>$0.00</value>
		</price>
	</prices>
	
	<press-contact>bkd@estudiovacaroxa.com.br</press-contact>
	<phone>+55 21 99810 6555</phone>
	<!-- <address>
		<line>Praça Comandante Xavier de Brito, 30</line>
		<line>Tijuca</line>
	</address> -->

	<socials>
		<social>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>twitter.com/estudiovacaroxa</link>
		</social>
		<social>
			<name>Facebook</name>
			<link>facebook.com/estudiovacaroxa</link>
		</social>
		<social>
			<name>Youtube</name>
			<link>youtube.com/estudiovacaroxa</link>
		</social>
	</socials>

	<description>
	Epic Golf 2D is an extremely casual golf game that offers a more modern and unprecedent take on the formula, making itself accessible to all audiences, with a learning curve that's not steep and manages to never gets boring. Plus thunders, explosions and a lot of BOSS BATTLES!

Inspired by classic videogame art, the game mixes a side view in 2D with unusual interactions with the environment, thus revealing a unique and innovative aesthetic. It's overflowing with nostalgia, and it's always stimulating the player's creativity in a fun way with its bold design.

We have a game that offers to the players the possibility to develop their own ways to play it, therefore, it has a huge potential to be expanded through DLCs or future instalments, adding new game modes, new characters, equipment customization and even themed golf courses.

It's easy to see that Epic Golf 2D distances itself from other golf games, as it presents a unique spin on the formula while it encourages the player to enjoy a game that’s both creative and elegant.

The idea is to develop a golf game IP with an arcade mode and a dynamic, challenging and fun gameplay, resulting in a game that's a joy to play, while also being incredibly addicting and with lots of replay value.
	</description>
	
	<history>
	The Estúdio Vaca Roxa is a group of friends formed by a common desire: "Make Games".

We learn together and we go a long way until we get inputs for the development of this game.

In a story of failures and twists, full of ups and downs, we learn to overcome our fears and continue to do what we love most. So we create games that we would like to play, and as players we know that when the work is done with due care the magic happens.

We idealized this game of golf in a super unpretentious way and at some point we were sure that we would be able to develop a game that would be a unique experience. In this way we will deliver the best we can while we can not do better yet.

It is rewarding to do what we like to do, even in free time in the middle of a super rushed routine. Some friends were infected and joined the team to help with development. Patricia, Gabe, Mauricio, Didi and we look forward to many others. Today we have a multifaceted team with one purpose: to make the best arcade golf game with boss battles and unlimited challenges.

It's a dream to be creating this game and we hope you enjoy our work. The Purple Cow is our dream barn.

Stay purple!
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>Extremely casual game, accessible to all audiences, it has a fast learning curve, without looking silly or aimed towards kids..</feature>
		<feature>Singular aestetic, mixing a 2D side view perspective and interactions with the envinroment, revealing the game mechanics' inovative atmosphere.</feature>
		<feature>Emergent gameplay mechanics and countless ways to tackle the courses.</feature>
		<feature>Fun, dynamic and challenging multiplayer that offers tons of replay value.</feature>
		<feature>BOSS BATTLE!!!</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Gameplay Video</name>
			<youtube>EaH979hUMrE</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>

	<awards>
		<award>
			<description>Finalist for this prestigious award</description>
			<info>BIG Starter, 27 June, 2018</info>
		</award>
	</awards>
	
	
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy> <!-- can be true or false -->
	<monetization-permission>monetize</monetization-permission> <!-- can be: 	false (no video allowed),
																			 	ask (permission on case-per-case basis),
																			 	non-commercial (no monetization allowed),
																			 	monetize (full permission) -->	
	<additionals>
		<additional>
			<title>Estúdio Vaca Roxa</title>
			<description>We love to create playful things.</description>
			<link>http://estudiovacaroxa.com.br</link>
		</additional>
	</additionals>
	
	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Wilson Melo (bakudas)</person>
			<website>www.wilsonmelo.com.br</website>
			<role>CEO, Artist and Designer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Marcelo Belkiman</person>
			<website>www.mmbelkiman.github.io/</website>
			<role>Artist, Freelancer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Patrícia Mani</person>
			<role>Artist, Freelancer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Gabe Fern</person>
			<role>Artist, Freelancer</role>
		</credit>		
		<credit>
			<person>Maurício Munky</person>
			<role>Musician, Freelancer</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>
	
	<contacts>
		<contact>
			<name>Inquiries</name>
			<mail>bkd@estudiovacaroxa.com.br</mail>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>http://twitter.com/estudiovacaroxa</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Facebook</name>
			<link>http://facebook.com/estudiovacaroxa</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Web</name>
			<link>estudiovacaroxa.com</link>
		</contact>
	</contacts>
</game>